There's a fire burning
at the back of the building!
Find the one who murdered Momoka,
then burn them in the Fire of Judgment.
A witch hunt? This sounds interesting.
The game has already begun.
Hey.
All right, let's search for the witch!
Hey, you.
Why weren't you with her today?
What?
Why were you late?
Weren't you always with her?
- Is she the witch?
- It's not me!
We'll know once we throw you in the fire!
I was in my room! I'm not lying!
You two were always together,
but today you happened to not be with her?
All right, it's decided. She's the witch!
Drag her to the fire!
- Come on!
- Hoist her up!
- Heave-ho!
- Stop it!
- Here we go!
- I didn't do anything!
Stop this!
Calm down.
Let go of Asahi.
There should be other suspects.
Where were you guys,
and what were you doing? Can you prove it?
Just say it!
Both of us were having
a good time in the same room, right?
Everyone will take turns reporting
what they've been doing in the past hour.
There's blood on her!
- Don't get the wrong idea.
- Now, this is getting interesting.
- Could she be the witch?
- You're wrong!
This is Hatter's blood.
- What?
- Hatter's blood?
I was checking Hatter's body.
That was when the blood got on it.
His body?
Hatter was murdered.
- Hatter was…
- Why did you keep it from us?
The executives believed
this would throw everyone into confusion.
Are you guys hiding
more things from us? Hey!
- Stop whispering among yourselves!
- Calm down!
This bullet was stuck
inside Hatter's body.
The firing marks align
with the firearms we have here.
What?
This means someone
at the Beach killed Hatter.
Hey. Could it be
that the witch killed Hatter?
I mean, doesn't that sound plausible
given the timing of the events?
The witch must be among them--
How troublesome.
Let's just burn everyone we find.
If someone among us is the witch,
then everyone
other than the militant member
is the witch.
Who's the witch?
Come forward.
If nobody does,
then I'll throw everyone into the fire.
- Oh, no!
- Run!
Hurry up!
ONE PER PERSON
Let's go!
Let's split up
and comb through the entire group!
Don't let anyone escape!
Are you really going to do this?
We were all allies!
What?
If the game doesn't end
after you hunt down everyone,
then we'll eventually
have to kill each other--
Burn him.
I have no need for useless people.
Let's go!
Suzuka, hurry up!
We have no time to waste
with these people.
Quick, hide inside this room.
Where are you going, Usagi?
I have to search for someone.
Please bring me along!
It's either Game Over or death for me
if I wait here.
Hey, it's me!
Let me help you!
You and Arisu helped me in a game before.
Help me search for Arisu!
Those guys are serious about that.
They're closing in.
Let's hurry!
Suzuka!
Stop it. Neither of us is the witch.
Hurry up and shoot.
Please.
Don't kill me.
I'll do anything!
Please. I beg you!
That is not human.
It's not a human!
All of them are nuts.
How unpleasant.
Why would they go so far just to survive?
There's no way
they'll find the witch like this!
The witch could be you, Kuina.
The same goes for you.
Lure them all out to the courtyard.
It's too troublesome
to move all the bodies.
There are still some
hiding inside the hotel, right?
I'll force them all out.
- Arisu!
- Arisu.
Arisu!
GASOLINE, KEROSENE
No!
Asahi?
Are you all right?
I can't do this.
Where is Arisu?
He's in the main building.
- Arisu!
Here we are!
Joe.
Fuck you, Saiko!
Where is Arisu?
Somewhere on…
the fourth floor.
You better be telling the truth.
I saw Niragi coming out of a room.
- Kuina?
- Hey.
What are you doing?
If you're free, can you lend me a hand?
Are you the witch?
Unfortunately, no.
What about you?
I guess not.
Anyone who's desperately trying
to identify the witch now
is not the witch.
If you were the witch,
you would have hidden yourself
to kill some time
or participated in the killings.
So what are you up to?
Searching for the witch.
Here it is.
What's that?
Cyanoacrylate glue.
In short, super glue.
What?
If we heat this up
and hold it over the murder weapon,
the cyanoacrylate vapors will fuse
with the moisture to show fingerprints.
Fingerprints?
Next, we'll use some cocoa powder
to dust for fingerprints
on things like cups that have been used
by the most likely suspects.
After we take the fingerprints with tape,
we'll be able to identify the culprit.
Just what did you do before coming here?
I was in Forensics
in the Tokyo Metropolitan Police.
I see. So we can clear the game like this.
You, go ahead.
What?
I'll leave it to you
to help us clear the game.
Fire!
Over here!
Someone, help us!
- Run!
- Hurry up!
Run to the annex!
Damn it!
Hey, aim properly!
Take your aim!
Take this!
- Did you see that?
- Hey!
I told you not to move!
Hey!
If you move again,
we'll make you eat that again.
Urine rice!
- Who's going next?
- I'll go!
Hey, stand up! Come on!
Are you listening, Niragi?
Aren't you sick
of bullying the weak already?
Where were you hiding?
There are tons of places for me to hide.
You really get on my nerves.
All the goddamn time!
You always act as if you're so clever.
But I am clever.
Perfect.
Let's put an end to this, shall we?
Not bad.
What did you do before coming here?
I worked in a clothes shop. Why?
Never hesitate to land the final blow.
- Damn junk!
- Stop it!
You're a boy,
so why do you need cosmetics?
Hikari.
Never come back.
Hikari? Hey!
Enough about me.
What about you?
The main power supply has changed
since the game started.
So?
Our electricity used to be
powered by generators.
Now it comes from the hotel's
main power source.
This means that the ones in charge
of the game snuck into the Beach
to control the power in the basement.
What are you trying to say?
I'm talking about
who the witch is, of course.
What else do we need to care for?
You're insinuating
that I'm the witch, right?
Sorry, but that's not possible.
Only the executives have information
on the main power supply management.
In the first place, only you guys
have the key to access the underground.
So I'll kill all executive members,
starting with you.
Do you think that I can't aim
at a short range with this rifle?
Yep.
You idiot!
What the hell was that?
Robert Edwin Peary.
He was an explorer who devoted
his entire life to reach the North Pole.
THE BOUND UNIVERSE
He failed many times, and even lost
eight of his toes to frostbite.
However, in 1909,
he became the first Westerner
to reach the North Pole.
I'm leaving your dinner here.
Ordinary people wouldn't understand
those like him, who embrace death.
However, I can tell
that they were shouting
about their freedom of living,
which includes such death.
What about me now?
Hey.
What should Mom do?
Born in a land where I can't even
eat raw liver through my own volition,
I was raised in an environment
that makes me unaware of death.
How can I feel truly alive?
Let me out of this temporary home.
I want to live in the real world.
And then, I came to this land.
Game cleared. Congratulations!
This is the first time
I have ever tasted it.
The freedom of living.
You.
I heard that you were a tattoo artist
in the original world.
Yes.
Tattoo something really awesome
all over my body.
Something so awesome that I won't be
able to live in the original world.
This is my declaration of will.
I will live in this land forever.
For me…
I have no past.
Oh, sorry.
I finally understand.
I've always thought
that you and I were similar.
Me and you?
Both of us despise our past.
I've finally decided because of you.
You just keep turning your back
on your past.
But I…
I will face my past once more
in order to survive!
Do you remember that arcade
that went down?
What was the name again?
It was in front of our high school, right?
- What was it again?
- Dream World?
It was Dream World!
Oh, right! It was Dream World!
I'd always skip classes to go there,
and Arisu would be there too.
He would be
reading out loud all the dirty articles.
The porn magazines from the '90s
were really the best.
Right, they had big dreams.
The reader submissions
were taken seriously.
They really sucked you in.
When the arcade went bankrupt,
Arisu stood
in front of the building and cried.
I didn't cry!
Those times were the best.
No matter how we complained,
high school life was awesome.
Arisu.
Live your life to the fullest.
Live your life for me, got it?
Someone…
Smoke?
What? Is there a fire?
I hear someone.
Hey!
Someone, help me!
He's in there!
Arisu!
The door won't budge.
I did it.
I can't do this anymore.
Arisu!
Usagi.
Is that all you can do?
I knew it. You and I…
Our will to survive is too different.
"Will to survive."
Was it?
Hikari.
You came back a totally different person.
But…
you look beautiful.
Mother.
"Never hesitate to deal the final blow."
I did as you told me,
Father.
I'm so glad.
You're safe.
Thanks.
I hate to break this to you now,
but we only have 30 minutes left.
Just explain the rule to me.
Out of ammo.
We killed so many
and still can't find the witch.
Just what have we done?
This is seriously the worst rule ever.
But just like those taggers
from the tag game,
who were made to participate
in the game with rules of their own.
I'm sure it's the same this time.
The witch has to kill the girl
to start the game
and survive
until the end of the time limit.
In other words, the witch clears the game
if everyone here gets a Game Over
or gets struck by the lasers.
Just who could be the witch?
If I were the witch,
I would join the others in the hunting
since it'll be Game Over if I'm caught.
So could it be someone from the militants?
Niragi, Last Boss, or Aguni?
No. If that's the case,
then the militants will kill one another.
But it doesn't feel like
the purpose of the game.
The purpose of the game?
This is a Ten of Hearts.
It's not just a physical game.
I know that
since I've cleared a Hearts game before.
Hearts games are utterly wicked.
You toy with people's feelings,
betray, and kill each other.
They're designed so that you can't win
without feeling disgusted.
If the militants win this way,
there will not be any conflict.
So what is it?
Something's weird.
What could it be?
If I were the witch,
how would I influence the game?
It doesn't suit you.
Who would've thought
that the best host in Kabukicho
would end up being a hatter?
I can't go against my father's dying wish.
You're an SDF officer too, right?
I thought
you could only belong to the yakuza.
Speaking of the yakuza,
Shogo was killed laying his hands
on the government's money.
You're the only old friend I have left.
Live long.
You too.
No.
I shouldn't be thinking like the witch.
I should be thinking like the game master!
Game master?
Don't you think this seems tailor-made
for the players, for this place,
and for this time?
After Hatter was killed,
Momoka was murdered.
Someone who knows
the ins and outs at the Beach
made this game
after calculating the timing.
They calculated the timing?
Their deaths did not just occur
at the same time by chance.
The game master had likely been
waiting for this moment.
Seriously?
Then who is the witch?
Hatter's death was made known
after Momoka died.
Those who knew of Hatter's death
were only the militants
and the executive members.
But the game master might have
known of Hatter's death somehow.
Then all the Beach members are suspects.
When I passed by the lobby
one hour before the game started,
Momoka's body wasn't there yet.
So someone moved her body
during that time frame.
There's no point in asking
since the witch can lie.
The question is…
Why did the game start now?
Why did they wait for Hatter's death
before they started the game?
It was to throw the Beach
into a state of chaos.
If that was the case,
if I were the game master…
Don't tell me…
I got it!
If we stop here,
then all we did would be pointless.
We can't stop now!
Time remaining, 20 minutes.
Arisu.
I think I know…
who the witch is.
Subtitle translation by: Qianni Lu